Hello friends, I welcome you to your
own
YouTube2 Management Company. Here
is the name of the company. The fundamental
market cap price of the entire company is given here.
You can check it here.
So let's start with the first
company for today, UTI Asset Management
Company. You can see here that an
update is coming from the company where it is being told that a
meeting of the Board of Directors has been scheduled on 29th April. Here the
company can announce its result and
dividend here. So the
important date will be 29th April 2025.
Let's move ahead now. Let's move
towards the next company where you can see the name is
Asl Technologies. Here is the name of the company.
And here also an important
update is coming from the company. Look here, it is being told
that there will be a two-day meeting on 21st and 22nd. The
meeting is going to be held here. Here the
company is going to announce its result and
dividend here. Two big
announcements will come from the company. The
important date will be 21st and  22 But
when will the important update come, so on April 22, the
update will come here on April 22, there will be a meeting for two days
but the update of the meeting will come on
April 22, 2025, where the company can
announce the result as well as the dividend here,
now let's move ahead, let's move to the
next company, where you can see its name
is III Lombard General Insurance Company,
its name is and here also you can see that the
update is coming from the company today itself,
see here it is being told that on
April 15th, the Board of
Directors meeting was scheduled
here, the company which is here can
announce its result as well as the dividend here,
so let's move ahead, let's move to the next
company, where you can see its name is
Ashiana Housing Limited, here is the name of the company
and here also the update is coming from the company,
yes see, it is being told that on
March 28, on March 28, the Board of
Directors meeting was scheduled here, where the
company which is here
can announce the dividend here now  Let's move ahead and
move to the next company where you
can see the name is Kansai Narol
Pints. Here is the name of the company and here
also you can see that an important
update is coming from the company. See here it is being told
that the meeting of the Board of Directors has been
scheduled here on 6th May.
Here the company
can announce the result and also the dividend here. Now let's move ahead and
move to the next company
where you can see the name is Kama
Holding Limited. Here is the name. Here also an
important update is coming from the company.
Here the company has announced a dividend today. You
can see that the amount of dividend is
huge, ₹1 7.75 paisa. ₹1 75 paisa
per share. The company has announced dividend here, that is, on
one set you will get ₹1 75 paisa. The
dividend and the dividend
of this dividend is fixed on 28th March, 28th March 2025.  It has been done
and see
when will the payment of this debit be made, it will be Tuesday,
the 22nd of April 2025. This debit will
also be paid by now. Now let's move ahead and move to the
next company where you
can see your name is Ranjit Metronics. The
name of the company is Market Cap etc. is quite
small. This company is not a profitable stock,
so trade carefully, it can be a risky
trade. There are
two big announcements coming from the company here.
Also, see, two big announcements are going to happen here,
one will be the surge split event and the
second is also an announcement regarding the bonus. The
ratio of the split which the company has fixed,
see, it is telling that the
face value of the shares you are currently holding is 10,
after the split it will change to five, so the
face value is changing from 10
to five, which means one share will become
two shares in your account. And along with this, there will be a
bonus here too, so the bonus ratio is 1:1, which
means you will get one bonus
here. And look at these two events.  You
can see what is recorded, so the 2nd
April 2025 has been fixed, so
what will be the last day to buy shares, if you
want to participate in this, then by 1st
April, if you buy this share and
keep it recorded, only then you will be
eligible for this corporate event, so now let's move ahead, let's
move to the next company,
where you can see the name is Mrigesh Trading
Limited, the name of the company is Mugesh Trading, the market cap
etc. is quite small, so there can be a little
risky trade here, so be careful,
here also the trade initiative
is Magaj Trading and here also an
important update is coming from the company, all are
coming regarding the split, that is, the
shares that you are currently holding will be
broken into multiple shares, it will be converted into
split shares whose face value is
currently one equity share, its face value
is 10, after the split, its face
value will become one, this means one share will become
10 shares in your demat account
and see here what is the reason
given for the split, so wider participation of small
investors so that small investors  This is being done to
increase investor participation and also to
increase liquidity here.
This update is coming from the company. Now see, the company has
announced the split, this does
not mean that it will be completed immediately, it will take
time, it is going to take two months here, you can
see here, the
expected time of
completion is, it is going to take two months here,
along with this I would also like to tell you
that in bonus and split, you do
not get any share for free, everyone
will say that you get shares for free, but you do
not get anything for free here because the
ratio in which the company gives you split
shares or bonus, its
price does not fall in the same ratio, so keeping that thing
in mind, you take any trade
initiative,
where you can see the next company, the
name is TVS Holding Limited,
and here you can see that
today from the company, there is a huge dividend
transfer of 93 rupees or you will get 93 rupees.  The
record date for dividend and deduct is
28th March, 20th March 2025. The date of record for this date has been
fixed. Now let's move ahead and move to the
next company where we
can see the name is Hindustan Unilever
Limited. The name of the company is Hindustan Unilever Limited and here also an
update is coming from the company today.
See here, we are telling you that on
24th April, the board of directors
meeting was scheduled where the company can announce its
result and along with that, it can
also announce a dividend.
So this is the update from Hindustan
Unilever. So let's move ahead now and
discuss about such stocks
where tomorrow is a big day.
Tomorrow is a big day for these stocks because here a
big announcement is going to come from the company.
Here in the name of the first company, PH
Capital, where tomorrow i.e. on
25th March, an update is going to come from the company.
Regarding deduct, the
record date for this day is 4th April 2025.
The record date has been fixed.
Now let's move ahead to the next company Virat Leasing
and see here also, tomorrow i.e. on 25th
March, an important
update is going to come from the company. Regarding the sub-division
split, an update can come here on
25th March. The next company is where you
can see the name is ADC India
Communication Limited. The name of the company is ADC India Communication Limited. And
here also tomorrow i.e. on 25th March, an
important update can come from the company.
Regarding dividend, an
important update can come. The
company can make a special inter-dividend announcement tomorrow.
Now let's move ahead, let's discuss about
such stocks where 24th
March was the last day to buy for all these stocks, that is,
if you buy these shares on 25th March, then
you are not eligible for the corporate event.
Here the name of the first company is Kesol,
where this
ex-deductible will be done on 75-750 paisa. The next company is Mishra
Dhatu.  The company has allowed a dividend of 75 paise per share here during the day.
This will become ex-debted tomorrow.
If you buy these shares tomorrow, then you are
not eligible for corporate debit. If you had
last debited these shares, then buy them by 24th March and
keep them till the record date, only then you will be
eligible for this corporate debit. Let's move
ahead where we will discuss about
25th March. 25th March is the
last day to buy shares for all these stocks. You
can see here the name of the company is
Dhanlaxmi Roto Spinners. Bonus issue event is
1:1 ratio, that means
you will get a bonus in exchange of one share here. Exit
recorded on 26th March. Next is RC
Limited. There is a debit of ₹3.60 paise. Exit recorded on 26th March.
TVS Motor Company D.
Exit recorded of shares at ₹10 on 26th March,
that is, till 25th March. If you buy these shares and
keep them till the record date, only then you will be eligible for this
corporate debit.  You will be eligible for this, so
this was the complete update regarding
stocks with corporate action, I hope you liked the video, please
like, share and
subscribe to the channel, thank you.